Long time ago
in the faraway galaxy
Star war
The third gathers
The backstroke of the west
The war came!
The republic encountered
Two squares fight the vehemence
The improbity fills the world
The space general
of the alliance is skillful
Kidnap the D the
speaker the conduct
The proper abruption
alliance troops tries
ratio prosperous drive with the
Target, teacher
Take aim at directly the
machine head of that airship
Is an airship that
that slowness crawl along
Good, I have seen
this is very easy
My important step six, receive
I are above at you
four machine am after death at me
General, I now is
to fights the appearance
Game time started
Our dichotomy opens the combat
He is in my behind
My distance his half kilometer
Not, let I to solve him
Notice the guided missile
pull out high!
The guided missile
can't beat the inside mine
Led to bounce back
Like, reach the man, Good good good
let us counter-attacking
You remain on standby
I use the backset equips
Two fix together
The disgusting thing came
True vexed
Is an airship robot
R2, you careful point
, God
Have to think that
the way stops them
I can then the close
quarter beats them
We must fly into the enemy's
commander airship finds
Good kind of
Do not beat, you can
not help me like this
I agree, my method
is not so good
Is really to bother
Do you fuck on I
Move to the right side
Not line
so we two would be over
You leave here
you can not help mine
I can of, teacher
Beat it, R2
Carefully
Reach the man
beat it the in-between eye
Good, you beat the
inside good kind of, R2
The airship of the
general in place ahead
You have and did not
notice he wanted to blockade
Sorry teacher
I walk first one step
, I feel far from good
R2, find the speaker
Speaker come out from here of
The robot can search
for with the machine
I think that I can
then extrication he to
I feel that this is a trap
Resemble the last time?
But we can will account
and then account
R2, come back
I need you foolish in ship
Take this, wait for the order
After all out what matter
Two persons entered the airship
we want to hinder them
Kill these two republics bodyguard
Exterminate them
Let go of the weapon
I said that let go of
Behind of the
person do not push
Put the proceeding
here over fight
Do you let it stopped?
Have no, is you? I have no
Were perhaps stuck to
We must go out, we must
be everywhere in search of
R2, telephone the steps is here
Is that what things?
R2, telephone quickly
the steps is here
Come back, there what too have no
R2, do you is fucking
, I was old
R2, R2
Stop the bottom
stop the bottom, R2
Raise the hand to, boy
R2, Did you hear me?
R2, let elevator risen
is not a descent
Hey, you!
Now, very good
Stupid robot
Very good
, is you
Is what is the row?
Always is a R2 to come to
Do not take the
elevator to do the game
Is all a disaster that R2 ask for
Is you make the ghost
I what did not do
Speaker
Does you is all good
We are very good
Is a time that we cooperated
I an individual
beats not is all right
You two careful, he is a big
Mr. speaker, we are for the big
Pull out your sword
Dedicate the body
for your speaker
You this time ran to do not drop
I always at wait for this day
Even since the last time
fights with you hereafter
My force has promoted two times
Very good, give me
surprised and pleased
Good!
Even since you I separate
I has been hating you
You are a sacrifice article
that I cut up rough now
Very good, the ratio
is prosperous, very good
Killed him, now killed him
I can't
Hurry
You make out quite good
Make him on the hoof
very dangerous
To, but he is not just a prisoner
I should not kill him
this not agree with
This very nature
he hewed away your hand
You also kill certainly he revenge
The business of the
vengeance is very familiar
Remember you to have ever
tolded me your mother's
Still there are those
pathetic people
We must leave here now
Otherwise they all at worry
gold
He big in nothing
important in good elephant
Do not take care of him
otherwise and too late
We can't throw down him
Beat, we are great
and black influences
Give your runway!
The elevator
was out of order
R2, come 3224
elevators are here
Stabilize the airship
Start all engines
Relax, this
circumstance we saw many
Slow, that is what?
R2. R2, let elevator stopped
A day after the fair
jump quickly
See can also must
not find out the exit
The airship returns at fly
R2, come down here
Superior, they have escaped
a day after the fair
I should really feeds you all dog
Order patiently
What is the row?
I said, toing have the patience
Good of, patience
To, the R2 came
right away in a moment
Then can make we out
Lo, all right
Raise the hand
Do you have what
to want to say
, liked too
Sir, you came finally
I always at expect your come
This is not the once successful
salvation activity, to
Welcome you
Just hopeless situation warrior
I think is what somebody
lntruded in to come
Space general, you and not
equal to I think severe
Smelly boy
We still have the mission
you do not ask for the him
Don't you ever think to
discovers here from I clues
This time we have no this plan
The this time your turn escaped
R2
Batter to death them
Leave he, run quickly
Useless, Sir
First aid airship
Giving first aid the already
disheveled hair projection
You feel that can
we drive this everybody's
That you need not anxious about
Under a certain circumstance
my driver the ability
Open to rise and fall
open to have to drive
The good elephant in
airship dropped what things?
Did not relate to
we the good elephant returns
The beginning accelerates
Speed 16
We entered the atmosphere
Keep speed
Rush out the atmosphere
Relax, R2
5000 rices are high empty
It is or so and each
to there is 5 airships
The front is a lemon avenue
flying straightly
The temperature of our
airship is too high
The nobody greets
Do you do not come down, teacher
, not, I am uninterested to politics
Your peace negotiations makes
progress to go to all right
And, you have the
prospect very much, you go in
Etc. , it is your idea
that one of this rescue
You do not forget, gold
Is you rescued the speaker
is you killed the
Is you saved I return to carry
on the back me a dangerous
But I am all to is trained by you
I do not like to set
foot in the politics
gold, today is your day
Your meeting celebrates
for a day of the honour
Like, record, you owe me a
You owed seven times
Is nine times in fact
Like, this time do
not calculate in fact
Mr. speaker
you return all right
Yes, I am good very
thank you to send the person
But, the general
space escaped again
The general space can
always succeed to succeed
He is very deceitful
He is to splits up the
doctrine alliance leads
And I guarantee to you
As long as he is on the hoof
The parliament will support
the war by voting
Mr. speaker we can
never compromise to black
The republican
national legislature
Again thankful parliament
Hear, they must not do so
Boon, I agree your
way of speaking
In fact, I a person can
also grasp the space
The war will continue
unless grasp the general
But I will do my the whole effort
Walk first one step, Sir
Oh, gold
Dear, how are you
Hear of you is killed
I did not die, is not
Apparently we will separate
the lifetime similar
While hearing of
the speaker were kidnap
I thought of that I want to
attend the salvation activity
Etc. , here not line
I had enough of
these politicseses
I think only of to
get married with you
Do not say these
Are you O. K.
You is shivering
How
Waiting for the happy
event condescends to come
Dear, I was pregnant
This... ...
This is really too stick
We should how do
I no longer worried
the other thing now
Good
This is a happy time
The most happy time
of inside of whole life
I came, west emperor
Space general I suggest
you have the abruption
All concentrates to transfer
the wood method star
That has completed, my host
The judgment day of world
come quickly, general
But we lost the
His dead is what doesn't matter
My new- accepted disciple
Younger than him, more severe
I living the child's
time you must at home
Make the home a little
bit more safe
I can breakfast for the new
house that baby tidy up it
It has a great father
A great hopeless
situation warrior
The beauty that
you are like this
I let me become
the beauty to your love
Not, I love you love deeper
Your meaning is
a love to tie up you
That is not my meaning
At least I say to half
Return my baby
You is missing what
Nothing important
I still remember the scene
that send your this
To spend how long does two
lovers talent open heart
Resemble a dream
Boon?
My dream arrived the scene for
mother to depart this life
Then
Dreamed you now
Tell me
Just a dream is just
You died at the time
of livinging the child
Is that baby on the hoof?
Do not know
Just a dream is just
I do not hope this dream true
Our baby will change our life
The queen will continue
to allow us as her loyal to
Then speaker his... ...
I know, I know
You feel that does
the child will help us
I do not need the child's help
Our baby blesses god'sly
Pregnancy? Pregnancy
After all does the dream
arrived the what kind of
Pain and sufferings
ache, death
Your oneself?
Or person whom you know?
Other people
Intimate person
Yes
You must be careful
Worry to lose
is to lead to the evil augury
I hope that these dreamses
really can't become
Death, is a life natural a part
Keep off to will carry
toward you to evil person
Take no notice of them
do not miss them
Lead long to pull with them
only will bring to envy
That is the dark beginning
Should I how do? The master of?
Train the oneself the
academic association
Abandonning the oneself
worries the lost thing
You missed the combat
report of the other warrior
Sorry, I occupied to delay
I give to do not lend out
It is brief to come to say
the meeting
Apparently I depraved
But the tile time
transfered the troops
What mistake does that have
The parliament plan
passes the vote give
This mean the less
freedom with more wars
Like this not good
Like this we can
sooner at an end war
Carefully of
your friend speaker
Carefully what?
He does not hand over
to send army the power
Why?
He do not say
He do so is not for the
sake of parliament
This often is falsely, to?
Everything is all not normal
This let me feeling uneasy all
I hope you to believe me, gold
Certainly
I need your help
young man
Your meaning is
I depend on you
Does needing me do what?
I do not understand
You is I face the public eye
ear, with voice
I appointment to office
you as the private
I?
Make the elder?
This honor and duties
is a lot too big
Parliament contain their member
they take nothing of
I miss their meeting of
They need you, you think
that the elephant do not
The parliament
admission D do so
The argument agrees the
D of adjust you into
I understood
You entered the parliament
we do not give the title
What?
Can be how like this
Like this too wide of the mark
Like this inequity
I can how belong to the
parliament but is not
You sit down first
young a line
Forgive me, elder
We have investigated of the
republic is systematic
Have no the trace and
shadow that discovers
To find out the space general
You must search for
the outer circle system
We had no superfluous airship
Do not send out
the air tank why
Send out right away the
tank go there very important
He cans say that again
that system is very
Let me going to, I relate to
with new hands quite good
That come to a decision so
The master of helps
the republic troops
Send these troopseses only
Is really boring
Let me enter the parliament
do not let me
Have no on the
republic history such
Town young man
you thered has been
You are so young and then
enter the parliament have
In reality, you the
relation of long peace
The parliament do not
like you like this
I swear to you, I did
not call the D of adjust
But that exactly you want of
You must make him doing
so with his comity
This has no relation
with our comity
The argument agrees the
speaker puts you into unique
Parliament all the
member trusts you
Does that how is again?
And I stands in your part
I do not want to make
What circumstances?
The parliament wants
to let you keep watch
They want to know him at fuck
They want to let do
I be the spy?
That is to rebels!
This is the war, gold
Give me this mission
in the parliament why
This mission is clandestine
Speaker D and is
not a bad person
Even since I came here
he is friendly to me
So you must help us
gold, our faith
believes in our religion
But is not to believe
in a certain person
He wants to make an
effort long hours occupy
Is a parliament decision
to let him continuing
Considers with your
felling once here
You are a discipline
to want to let me oppose
Objection republic
Objection morals
oppose the friend this
Why you want to let me doing so
Because the parliament
call you doing so
The gold did not produce any
enthusiasm to this mission
Put the gold with the D of
two together very dangerous
I feel that this
child cans not handles
I distrust him
Difficult way he is not
a parliament group to be
Difficult way he
under the past have no
So the elder all how says
We all like him
He is a right candidate
He can't let me disappointing of
have always been to have no
I hope you right
Sometimes I too so after
all the republic was how
That war has no well arranged
order to disrupt the republic
You had to think perhaps we stands
at the bad person's part
You are what mean
Why we loyal to democracy
nonexistent any further?
Why republic a war machine
at demolish everything?
I dare not believe
Your tone resembles
an abruption doctrine
This war represented
your mistake
Your peace negotiations
grows now the most close
Everybody want
that say to you
Let him stop the war
Do not let me do this matter
Say the words of some
representative's justice
You say what
Nothing important
Do not be like this
Do not shout to me
let me help you
Embrace me. Resemble
at pull the cloth by the
Resemble long time ago
in the world only
Have no the politics
have no the D of
You wish to see I is
speaker
To, gold, close to the amount
I have a good news
I beat the intelligence
bureau the telephone
They discovers the directions
of the space general
He hides at particularly
with the system of
Found out finally
I should hold tight
this devil to end war
I worry the collective
intelligence of the parliament
They did not send you
carry out this mission
Current you are the best candidate
Sit, back the bottom
gold, you know that I can't
depend on this parliament
And they bring into you
too in the scheme, hear
I am not that understand
You are affirmative
to have doubted
The hopeless situation
parliament wants to rule
They plan the betrayal me
I not think so
gold, careful want
You understand of, to
I know that they
do not believe you
To, all councilmans
whole republic
Our cognition hereafter
one of my thought
Why
They force you to do what not
the affair of the brilliance
They let you keep
watch on me
I not... ... I do not know
and should how say
Remember your the day of
the warrior study of the past
Have the person
who have your power
Even hopeless situation elder
The hopeless situation
elder is what justice
Justice
to see from which aspects see
Hopeless situation elders at
similar to others are all
Include to look forward
to to the right
But the west emperor
depends on the improbity
They consider
the oneself only
I also belong to the hopeless
situation Presbyterian
Hopeless situation elder should
be to have no private
They only concern
other people
Did you heard of the tragedy
that reach the man
Not
I think to be too is not
I think that the hopeless
situation elder also can't
That is a legend
Reaching the man cloth
space is the emperor
He is so strong and big
He even can use the original
dint to create life
He is very deep to black
influence understanding
In fact he can come back
from the brink of death
The black influence can
the matter that many supermans
But other people thinks that
these are what can't attains
The black influence
howed is afterwards
He become more and
more strong and big
Lost his power afterwards
afterwards he died
In fact he teaches own the
whole skills all to disciple
Then his land killed him
to let him going to bed
Satirizing the meaning is
he can let other people
But is incapable for
dint to the oneself
I can be then academic
association this kind of magic
Do not do the hopeless
situation elder can
We are republicans soldier
The space
general hasn't appeared
The information expresses
the space general
I can attain, I must
Hold tight the space general
and then can end war
We must be fast to
hold tight him accurately
Speaker the decision
lets me coming forward
Parliament would who oneself
decide to send to go to
Speaker the
decision was not
But the gold even
has experience of
I think
the card ratio can go to
I agree
Very good, parliament Sir
We were already the
whole to is ready
The current time arrived
commanding officer
Yes, master
They will need still
finally my I agree
Ignore at the beginning noisy how
The result is always like this
Master I let you disappointing
I feel grateful you very
much to my cultivation
I always eyes inside no man
I apologize to you
I was just made by the
Presbyterian Church
You are very strong very
astute I feel the pride
You still a child's time
I did your teacher
I learn the whole life to
all to teach to you
And you also became
greater than what I hope
But you want the patience
Allah gold
Very quick Presbyterian
Church will award your
ratio tile, the wish power
are together with you
Saw again, my friend
The wish power are
together with you at
Unfortunate of is
great majority city all
On the pimping
mainland in this area
At you before arriving
I will have been leading
But you did not
drag along too long
You trust, we let you
disappointing never
That liked too only wish
before you arrive
We did not
exterminate all enemies
Keep your energy do
not abandon forever
ratio the tile comes here
come this morning come
He how he is worrying you
He says that you bear the
very big pressure certainly
I feel to be fond
of the very much fan
What mean
ratio tile with Presbyterian
Church all distrust
They use their
life letter term you
Some matters took place
I can not become the
hopeless situation that
I do not want that just
keeps present condition
You are too high to
own expectation value
I found out to save your method
Save me
I saved you in evil-foreboding dream
Having what lets
you vexed heart
I do not want to lose you
the gets the rice
I guarantee die me to also will
feel happy with you together
Not, let I to guarantee
Please accept my salute
great hopeless situation
Is what breeze blow you
We this faraway place
Very unfortunate because of war
Unless you take to come over
can't have the war here
I want to ask you to grant
Can let us get the some fuel
Then for matching with the
space in not the general
I want to regard as
your city to our base
Here we follows
hostage just like
Someone is keeping watch on us
I am complete understand
Only have a little bit
the immodesty we all lose
Tell your people to seek
the refuge shelter quickly
lf you have the warrior kill
the time of the arrived
Please carry out
right away my order
Tell the section
I have contacted good
He has to say that he
have how much warriors did
Need not how long the troops
of the republic will arrive
I send now you carry
out the mission
However you only is
foolish on this star
You is safe
Safety prime minister
you think only of to flee for
We may be how safe I doubt
very much you can guarantee
Please believe me hear my
words you would the high
Your ship have too arrived
Everybody is good
Section ratio general
You is really a day of brave
Killed him
You rolls a little bit far
Let old man come to
dealt with this hopeless
You are the man of
you were played with
I once in your hopeless
situation encampment
Come, section ratio
Ignore you to how struggle
you died to settle
I can not think so
Master they proceeded to interfere
The section compares
the general with space
We are fights with the soldier
Thank you, commanding officer
Allah gold report this
to prime minister
The report want to
let the person feel
Is, master
I feel someone wants
to exterminate
Also is around prime
minister of dark power
lf he refuse to do not
hand over he is given
That he should go out
of power right away
The hopeless situation
Presbyterian Church
The dark power is
more and more strong
Prime minister
I just receive the
report that section
He is in handle
space not the general
That is a big challenge in
I should with he together
The Presbyterian Church
like enjoys you not
You not strange do they
do not seal you as the
I hope me to know
I feel more and more
I was been isolated by this
I know that still have
an esse for they having
They distrust you
Allah gold
They foresaw your future
They know that your
power will big outrun
This will be an
unprecedented affair
Please let me to help
you to the deeply thought
You are what how can
anyone know this power
My tutor tells me an
affair concerning it
Even include the innate
character of the dark
You know the dark
Allah gold, if a person
wants to comprehend
That he must the square
who study it the square
But a little bit much more
than only concerning
lf you like to be
a leads more astutely
That you must accept
this more great power
But want the caution
hopeless situation Allah gold
You only ask for help
me then can become the
The knowledge of the
dark of the study hopeless
In the fire of water
You say what
I begged you
using my knowledge
You are the governor
of this city
I know is what make
you feeling vexed
Hearing me says
Do not hope that rotting
hopeless situation
Even since does
I acquaint with with you
I know you at purpose
that look for the life
You are unwilling to
do a mediocre hopeless
You want to stand out
concerns the history
Do you want to kill me
I think certainly
I know
I can feel your exasperation
It let you concentrating on
Also make you stronger
I will tell the hopeless
situation Presbyterian
Certainly, you should this
But your indetermination
they will disdain
I am very quick and
then will find out the
You have got the
outstanding intelligence
Your intelligence may let
you understanding the power
It saved me and to support to me
Looking me am
a civilization person
Text how big teachers
I occupy to want to
Liked too
I just receive the concerning
report comparing much
I want to be certain is
prime minister to would
His urgent back up motive
He can't of
And I just know
an astonishing news
I think the pudding
that the prime minister
West
Yes, is a person
who we want to seek
You are how can anyone know
He knows which power source is
He also onces receive
training how to use
You are certain beyond all doubt
True regret we has
been having no the
Must take action as
soon as possible like this
Master, the prime minister's
power is very big
You arrest does his
hour need my help
Do not take care of this
matter this is to
I feel you these young
captivation in the publics
You a judgment for doing
also comes amiss easily
I must attend, master
Not line
lf what you say is true you
will get my trustful of
But now, you are foolish here
Until elder before
coming back wait for here
Is, master
You do not know, to
lf I were killed so any
save her opportunity
All lost
Text how big teachers
I think the space in not
I miss that I will hear
right away with my a just
Pull the name of the gram
republic with the space
You were caught, prime minister
You is threatenning I
hopeless situation master
The Senate will
decide your destiny
I am the member of Senate
Not just
That I have to revolt
Adult, you were caught
Allah gold, I told you you
will arrive to come here
My that's right
The hopeless situation
will pass in examination
The west ages is already
on doing not reply
You failed
Not
Not... you just failed
Die. . you are the country of
Take away this
power save your lover
You must use it
Do not hear his
Allah gold
Help me quickly
I cans not insists how long
Save me, Allah gold
I... I no longer...
I will solve you to
You must not
He must accept to interrogate
He controls the Senate
with the law court
Make him live
down too dangerous
My great void is
weak do not kill me
This is not the style
of the hopeless situation
He musts be live to
descend to go to
I need him
Beg you, not...
Get to say with you
that part forever
I did what
You completed your usage
Allah gold
Do my student
Study the dark power
in usage with me
You want me to do
what all line
Only guarantee my
cuckoldry the safety
Have no her me live
not descend to go to
This kind of power that
I say still only thered
But if our two people cooperation
I think that we can succeed
I would like to throw
in your door is next
Good of good
Your power is very strong
and big you will become
There is this power
You the meeting was
called by the person
Reaching the west of reaches
Thank, teacher
Get up
Young person, since the
Presbyterian Church does
They also can't teach you
certainly more knowledge
They are just a flock of
to fish for fame its person
Even act as rivals
with the Senate
You can say that again
Presbyterian Church
next move act
Would be to deal
with the Senate
lf still there is an esse
of hopeless situation
Include your friend
They will become the
enemy of the republic
I know, master
Have to hurry the activity
hopeless situations
lf they can't be exterminated all
The local war has no
the for the meeting
First, I want the temple
that you go to hopeless
Go to exterminate
your enemy there
Doing you needses must its matter
Do not hesitate
Do not show consideration
Only like this you then
can become the power
Like this you then can
save to return to your
That other hopeless
situation in the galaxy
We come step by step
You kill off all hopeless
situation in the temples
We take next move action again
Kill off all the remaining
hopeless situations
But the west will
rule the galaxy again
Enjoy the peace again
Insists to live hurry...
Walk quickly...
Commanding officer
contact your troops
Call them going to
a little higher place
Good of, Sir
Say the bottom conveniently
Thank you, section
We have to hurry to act now
Yes, Sir
Section commanding
officer time is up
That hopeless situation
killing off just now
Yes, host
Hurry
It is quick to come
The dynasty opens fire 66, 60:00
My host soon be finish
A line, their person is
too many we want to how do
Prime minister's office
says the hopeless situation
Do not worry I believe
his meeting has no matter
Out here what matter
Took place the
insurrection, superior
Do not worry, the
circumstance has suffered
Execuse me, superior
you should leave
That is all right
Hopeless situation
Run
Do not worry, let them walking
Hurry to find
out them yes, superior
See again
drag along the see again
I will miss your
We still hope from this
disaster inside some
Have to find out the
section pulls the ratio
Hurry to call last
airship in your person, hurry
Urgent circumstance code
913 did not contact
The section pulls the
ratio please say
ratio the adds the senator
My troops suffers the
raid I need help
This circumstance we
have received the report
Look your loss very
miserably heavy
Kiss too loudly
Are you O. K.
I know that the hopeless
situation temple suffered
I am very good, I just
worry you with the child
Out what matter
The hopeless situation
wants to overthrow
I see with own eyes the
text how big teachers
Allah gold you want to how do
I can't rebel against republic
I will be loyal to the prime
minister with Senate
Still have you
That ratio tile I do not know
Many hopeless situations
were all killed
I a hope hopeless situation
is woulded be loyal
I am frightened, Allah gold
I am keeping the destiny
everything will like
The prime minister gave me a count
Abruption doctrine come
together in the virtuous
I want to go to
be over this war
Wait for here
I come back
Everything will become
different of I guarantee
Wait for me certainly
Where does he want to go?
Do you must walk
Take good care of, my kid
Lady, have what can I help of
Have no, thank, blow the skin
I feel the... ...
to have no to help so
Have still how much
hopeless situation
Who also do not know
the ratio is prosperous
The like thousands
enemy assaulted
So I just come to seek the
Do we made to contact
with the temples
I have issue
to retreat the order
The speaker has requested
all hopeless situations
Cheat to say that
the war has ended
That we must return
lf take place what matter
they will be killed of
Your meaning is an
order to withdraw
To, elder, our person
is too dangerous
I agree
Only there is
knowledge can just point
My host, the enemy
hases pressed you
You handles affairs dint
You waits for my
disciple reaches of come
He will look after you
We receive the
information of a hopeless
Connect the yes superior
Councilman's that
the speaker requests you
I will go to of
He waits you there
May be a trap
I not think so
The impossible control
in speaker is several
Come to guarantee the
parliament intact well
They open the special
meeting of a parliament
They will become the
person of entering
R2, watch the airship
Welcome you, my host reaches
The current
situation has published
What is the row
We discovers the
purpose of hero's ground
Is to overthrow the Senate
Hero's ground will be
driven out and vanquish
Whether child can exist or not
He is not a gram
at least person
I hope that he can exist
This is what who fuck
Want to assassinate my
person to leave the scar
Became me disable and sick
However my power has
always been to have no like
For insuring the future
safety with prospers
The republic organizes afresh
Become the empire
of the first choice
This is for the sake
of a more safe the society
The freedom has died
In the voice of under
The war has ended
Please reserve our life
I change the password afresh
The hero that warning
is all ground keep distance
Wait until the gram
the person discovers
Will use very long hours
Wait a little
while the teacher
I need to know a matter
That is the safe password
if moved it
Only will result in
your pain and sufferings
I need to know the true
facts, teacher
Impossible
You are already
at full cock now
Spread all over
the place the empire
I hear not went to down
We must ruin the west
Let me kill the emperor
I can't kill the
peaceful willing to
lf want to do so you
return not enough strong
He the my brothers
in elephant is similar
I can not do it
A line have beened
distorted by the dark world
You the trained boy
noed longer is already
Drive dark world to gobble up
I do not know that the emperor
sends him to go where
Which does I do not
know to go to seek him
Can use your intuition
and then can find out him
You see last time he is when
Yesterday
Know that he is now at where
Do not know
The plum of, I need you help
He has the very big danger
West vital part he?
Is himself
The plum of
the peaceful is willing
Your mistake, you can how
say this kind of words
I in whole photographing
See him at kill the child
The peaceful is
willing to can't of
Absoluteness can't
He was cheated by the lies
we are all
The superior is the
whole acts the latter
Include the war
We have no and can
avoid this war
The ever since that
time willing to dies
The peaceful is willing to and
then become his
I do not believe
Do not believe
The plum of
I must find out him
You are to do not kill him
He now is a very big intimidation
Not line
The peaceful willing
to is the child's father, is
Really very sorry
Lady, let me
accompany you to go to
Can't in danger of
Let myself going to
this is the private matter
Literally you, lady
But I agree you
in no case like this
I can't have problems of
captain
This is the matter that
I must personally
Skin too would
at protect me behind
The operation that
I acquaint with it more and more
The barbarian has solved, host
So this matter has ended
Very big in your
Bring the Milky Way the peace
There is information
giving the space craft
Is systematic and must
close right away
All right, host
I see your ship
How run here
I worry you very much
They tell me concerning
you terrible affair
What affair
He says a member that
you become dark world
Say you at kill the child
The ratio wants
to let you leave me
He concerns us very much
We?
He has known
He wants to help you
The peaceful is willing to
I a hope gets your love
The love can't save you
the plum of
Only there is my new
ability then can save you
Why such, you are a good man
Do not do like this
I can't lose again your
elephant loses my mother so
I am more more than any hero's
geologic change's strong and big
I do so is for protecting you
Leave with me together
Helping me brings up our child
At the time of
we still canning make
Leave the all these
You unknown white, we do not
need to flee from home again
I bring the republic the peace
I am stronger and
big than superior
I can overthrow him
We can rule the
galaxy together
Become us to the
world to hope so
I dare not believe
the words that I hear
The ratio says of to
you changed
I do not want that hear
again the name that compare
Hero's ground rebeled me
You must not rebel me
I am already incognizant you
the peaceful is willing to
You let me feeling sad
I can't walk last with you you
a road for running about
Because ratio?
Because your
conduct and actions
The plan of your future
Stop right away
ask you to come back
I love you
Lier
Do not want
You follows he together
You take him to come to
want to kill off me here
Is not
Putting her walks
the peaceful is willing to
Is you let her rebel me
This is your own masterpiece
You can't rend away her
This is what your
exasperation results in
You let the dark lord
distort your heart
Now...
You become you to think
the ruined object before
Do not say the reason
with me, ratio
I have seen the true facts
of pure hero's ground
I not elephant you be
afraid the dark world so
I give my new empire
Bring the peace, freedom
Justice, with safety
Let me killing your and
is not your new empire
The peaceful is willing to
But is I to republic with
democratic and loyal to
lf you are not to stands at me
That you are my enemy
Disabled person must solve
I needs must I should of
Come
I see you to cut
up rough very much
Or should say that
is a dark improbity
Vanquish is
You surrendered
Surprise
Your pride let
you say such words
You will experience the power
of the dark world completely now
I wait for every moment
for this already a long time
My small manikin
Finally of hero's
will soon perish
Can't of, we wait and see
Do not draw a conclusion too quickly
time is it's yet early
lf you are so strong and big
why to leave
You can't obstruct I
I would be aller strong
and big than anyone
I underrate you to the
confidence of your apprentice
You unique trusting is
the power of the dark world
Hurry
We must leave
Leave after readying to
Did not see his corpse
So he did not die
Return again to look for
Is, follow instructions
Prepare my space craft
do to set out right away
Is, host
I felt the hero an in danger
I must leave the country
I found out you
the peaceful is willing to
I should know a scheme for
wanting to take over early
The peaceful is willing to
D the superior is a bad person
To me hero's is just bad person
Friend you are crazy
Your dead period arrived
teacher
Everything ends
the peaceful is willing to
The geography that
I stands compares you superior
You underrated my ability
Is
You drive the person who pick out
You this should ruin them
ising not to join them
Bring the world brilliance
But is not to bring the blackness
I will ruin you
The peaceful is willing to
you the past is my brothers
What I love is you
The willing to compares host
the plum of is very weak
Please must take a look
the peaceful is willing to O. K.
Big king, this place
He returns incredibly on the hoof
Grasp the person right away
Is, follow instructions
Execuse me
particularly reach the master
The compares the willing
to ratio the contact ascend we
Sending her goes to
medical treatment, hurry
Check result
she complete health
But we can't explain
why she quick dead
Does she die quickly?
We do not know why
She loses the live descending
the will that go to
We must proceed the surgical
operation right away
Talent extrication child
Child?
Is twins
Come to see your mother
See me
See
Relax
Come to see your mother
Is what woman
The compares
I wanted to leave
I am not line
I know, I know
south host
Can hear me
Yes, host
Where is the plum of
Her safety, is she O. K.
Under your
exasperation you killed her
Impossible
I can feel she
return on the hoof
Do not want
The child must hide
in the safe place
Must take they go to a
Can't drive the place
that west realize
The speed want to be quickly
I will take the
girl with the wife
We have been hoping
to get to keep the daughter
We will love hers
Boy
His family will hope what
I will look after this child of
We will disappear
until appropriate time
The willing to
compares the master
The time that you
make a living alone
I want to provide
a training to you
Train
There is an old friend
academic association the
An among those returned
to the another world
Your old teacher
I will teach how you
are communicate with him
This with in captain
Is
These childses hands
over to you to take care of
Like to like to
look after them
Clean them
I occupy to walk first
Is my wife
What
Over